resumebucket.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - Free Resume Builder

_**Effective Date: 4/16/18**_

Thank you for visiting a **Free Resume Builder** and **BOLD LLC** (“Provider,” “we” or “us”) offering. To help inform you, we provide this notice (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of personal information you submit or we collect through our family of websites that link to this Privacy Policy as well as our other related mobile websites, mobile Provider applications (“mobile apps”), services, tools, and other applications that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Site”). The Site is owned and operated by Provider.

## Privacy Policy Highlights

Please also read our full Privacy Policy

Personal Information Collected

  * When you register an account, use our services, use our Interactive Forum, or make a purchase, you voluntarily share certain personal information with us (e.g., your name, e-mail address, address, mobile number, and/or credit card information).
  * You may provide us with additional personal information (e.g., regarding your employment history, skills and work interests) when you view and interact with our features, and functionality, including posting your resume, career profile, cover letters or other information on the Site.

Tracking Technologies (Cookies)

  * We use tracking technologies such as cookies and other similar technologies to measure usage and provide information that will be of most interest to you. More info
  * We may collect additional information from you if you access our Sites through a mobile device (e.g. unique device identifier, device’s operating system, mobile carrier).
  * You may also provide us with information when interacting with our content through or linking to third-party social media sites, plugins, or applications.

Uses, Retention and Storage

  * To operate our Site and contact you and third parties at your request.
  * You agree that we can use the information as long as you have an account for the time and reasons outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Disclosure of Information

  * By using this Site you agree that we may share your personal information and other information we collect with the following entities: (1) our Corporate Family; (2) our service providers; (3) other entities, such as potential employers or job posting third party websites, with your consent; (4) legal and law enforcement; (5) others if there is a change of control; (6) ad networks; (7) companies in the mobile app industry; and (8) social networks.

Your Information Choices

  * You can control how and when you want to receive notifications from **Great Sample Resume** on the Site or by following instructions within the notices you receive. Click here for your other information choices

Access and Review Options

  * You can change your information at any time by editing your profile, deleting content that you have posted, or by closing your account. You can also ask us for additional information we may have about your account at customerservice@bold.com.
  * We may retain certain information if required by law.

Notification Regarding Updates

  * You agree that we may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting notices on this Site.

Contact

  * Questions about our Privacy Policy or about our handling of your information may be sent to privacy@bold.com or as otherwise set forth in the Privacy Policy.

## Full Privacy Policy

1\. Scope and Consent

Provider is an online destination that provides resume and cover letter building, career tests, salary information and other products and services for individuals seeking to further their career! We do not guarantee employment for any user of this Site. Nor do we guarantee that any employer will find qualified candidates through this Site. When you use the Site, you are contracting with Provider. If you reside outside of the United States Provider is your data controller. By using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

2\. Information We Collect

a) Registration, Product and Account Information: You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information (i.e., name, email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, credit card information or physical contact information) about yourself. If you register for an account with us, post a resume, create an email account using our platform, or use some of our products and services you choose to give us your personal information and are not anonymous to us. When you register an account or use certain of our products and services, create a profile, create a resume, search for or purchase products, create an email account on our Site, or otherwise engage with our Site, you may provide certain personal information (e.g., username and e-mail address). You may also provide payment information (e.g., credit or debit card information, name and billing address) to purchase products and services. Personal information is only associated with your account/profile when you sign in as a registered user.

b) Information to respond to your requests: You may give us your personal information so we can respond to your questions and requests as well as send you newsletters and other communications you request. Details of how you can opt-out of receiving any communications from us are detailed in the section headed Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information

c) Social Media Information: We may offer sign-on services that allow you to use third-party login credentials to access the Site. We also may offer services that allow you to share information with third-party social media websites such as Facebook, Google Plus, Twitter, and others.  
When you link your account or engage with our Site through third-party social media sites, you understand that you may be allowing us to have ongoing access to certain information stored on those social media sites (e.g. your social networking credentials, your public profile, friend list, people you follow or who follow you, pictures, your e-mail address, birthday, work history, education history, interests, current city, religious and political views, website, personal description, and likes, and your friends’ birthdays, education histories, personal descriptions and likes).  
We may also receive other information (e.g., content viewed and information about the advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on, etc.) from your interaction with our Site. You agree that we may share your video viewing with or obtain information about your video viewing from, analytics providers and advertising partners and third-party partners and social media sites for two years or until you withdraw your consent.

The information we have access to from the third-party social services varies by service and is controlled by your privacy settings on that service and by your consent. Information that may be passed to analytics providers and advertising partners may be via cookies and tracking technologies. Please see our Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy for information, including your choices in relation to some of these technologies. By associating an account managed by a third-party with your Provider account and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may collect, use, and store information from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

d) Information From Other Sources: The information we collect may be combined with information from outside public records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, additional contact information) that we have acquired in accordance with the law.

e) Mobile Information: With your consent we may collect additional information from you if you access our Site through a mobile device (e.g. your unique device identifier, device’s operating system, mobile carrier, location or GPS/geo-location, mobile number, your text messages, e-mails or e-mail address, user name, contacts/address book, financial or payment information, web browsing history, photos, your phone’s name, passwords, political interests, sexual orientation, racial or ethnic origin, religious and philosophical beliefs, trade union membership.

f) Technical Usage Information: When you visit our Site, we collect usage information sent to us by your computer, mobile, or other access device that tells us how you are using the Site including video-viewing, site views, key stroke data, mouse movement, scrolling, clicks, and typing (“usage information”). We use tracking technologies (including cookies, flash cookies, unique device identifiers, web beacons/GIFs, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browsers, cross-device tracking) to collect usage information. We may use tracking technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

Operationally-Necessary. We are not required to obtain your consent to tracking technologies that are operationally necessary.

Performance-Related. We may use cookies or other tracking technologies to assess the performance of the online services, including as part of our analytic practices to improve the content offered through the online services. For example, as set forth in our Cookies and Trackings Technology Policy, we use Google Analytics and Inspectlet to perform site analytics.

Functionality-Related. We may use tracking technologies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited the Site before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest.

Targeting-Related. We may use tracking technologies to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on our online service and third-party sites based on how you interact with our advertisements or content as well as track the content you access (including video viewing). Further information on this, and your opt-out choices, is below.

We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and/or connection information. During some visits we may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information.

Our goal is to collect and use only that information that we think is required for our legitimate business interests, in order to better understand your interests and improve your experience of using the Site. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or Social Media for up to two years or until your consent is withdrawn. To learn more about how we use tracking technologies and cookies, see Section 7 of this Privacy Policy.

g) Apply Tool Privacy Notice and Information We May Collect. We may automatically collect certain information (including Personal Data) from your device or web browser. We may automatically collect information from location storage associated with your web browser, including your browsing behavior for career searching activity. We may also automatically record your interactions with certain webpages by accessing local storage associated with your web browser. The Apply Tool was made to automatically interact with third party websites, so we may also collect some non-personal data about you when you visit those websites including, clickstream data, operating system being used, the URL of the site you have come from and move to after your visit, data relating to your activities on third party websites (including IP addresses and URLs) via tracking technologies (such as cookies and measurement software), the date and time of your visit and your server’s IP address, the geo-location of your device, and the type of payment you use. We collect this information for statistical purposes to find out how our website and the Apply Tool are being used. We may use this information to evaluate and, hopefully, improve your experience. As an example, when you visit a webpage that supports the autofill function, we may record metadata generated by your web browser that identifies one or more autofill fields that you interact with. In this example, we may also access local storage associated with your web browser to determine information (including Personal Data) which can be or has been entered into an autofill field. We use your information to facilitate your completion of job applications across the internet, on our websites and third-party websites and to provide advertising and/or other content that we believe may be of interest to you based upon your browsing behavior on the internet.

3\. Uses, Retention and Storage

a) Operate Our Site and Provide You With Our Services: We use the personal information we collect including e-mail account you might create on our platform using Provider mail to (i) respond to your questions and requests; (ii) provide customer service (e.g., to fulfill product and service orders made by you, give you information about your account to resolve disputes, problems with your account/profile or the Site, administer a contest, sweepstakes or promotion, or to provide information to third parties at your request such as potential employers, job matching services or third party websites, or other career related services); (iii) personalize your experience by providing content on the Site, including targeted advertising or job-related advertising, that we believe may be of most interest to you; (iv) improve the Site; (and (v) provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience.

b) Analyze and Aggregate Non-Personal Information: We use aggregate information about our users and non-personal information to analyze Site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports.

c) Prevent Fraud: We use information from the Site to prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, security breaches, and potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use.

d) Communicate With You and Third Parties at Your Request: We use your information to contact you to maintain the Site, your account, or to comply with your stated communication preferences, or to provide other products or services requested by you, as described at the time when we collect the information from you, or to contact you for other purposes authorized by law. If you have chosen to participate in some of our career building Services, the information you share with us may be provided to third parties such as (i) resume editors, (ii) employers or recruiters who might contact you about career opportunities, (iii) employers seeking candidates and/or (iii) other career service providers.

e) Mobile Data: When you access the Site on a mobile device, with your consent we may use the information collected for any purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content.

We retain personal information for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, our business purposes and/or to comply with the applicable laws, and your consent to such purpose(s) remains valid after termination of our relationship with you. You consent to our retention of your video viewing tracking data for as long as permissible under applicable law – up to one year after you close your account or otherwise withdraw consent for video tracking.

4\. Disclosure

Information we collect may be shared with:

a) The Provider Corporate Family and Other Third Parties: We may share the information we collect about you with the Provider corporate family (our affiliates as well as with third party suppliers. The information may be disclosed (i) to provide joint content and our products and services (e.g., registration, transactions, employment or education opportunities, analytics and customer support); (ii) to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud and/or data security breaches; and (iii) to guide decisions about our Provider or third party’s products, sites, applications, services, tools, and communications. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications and you will have the opportunity to opt-out in e-mail communications.

b) Service Providers and Other Third Parties: We may disclose your information to service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as, but not limited to, fraud investigations, bill collection, payment processing, and site analytics and operations). With your authorization, we may also share your information with potential employers, career/job-posting websites.

c) Other Entities with your Consent: We may share your personal information with third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (such as resume editors, employers, recruiters or job posting third party websites or others about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). On the Site, you may have opportunities to express interest in or register for other products and services. If you do, we will provide information about you to those third parties, or parties working on their behalf, to implement your request.

d) Legal and Law Enforcement: Law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third parties, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other Provider user to legal liability. In such events, we will only disclose information relevant and necessary to the investigation or inquiry, such as name, city, state, ZIP code, telephone number, e-mail address, user ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and anything else we may deem relevant to the investigation.

e) Change of Control – New Owners: Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will make reasonable efforts to request that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information would be used contrary to this policy, we will request that the new owner provide you with prior notice and depending on the circumstances, an opportunity to opt-in to or opt-out of the new use.

f) Ad Networks: On the Site, we may work with third parties to serve advertisement, provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement and site analytics and assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own tracking technologies/cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They might also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit and other information about you or your device in order to analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Site and elsewhere. For more information about third party ad servers at our Site and your ability to opt-out of targeted advertising from such third parties, please visit https://www.aboutads.info/choices/ which provides information about certain companies that we may be using to serve advertising on our Site.

g) Companies In The Mobile App Industry: If you access the Site through a mobile device or app, we may also share your information with Carriers, operating systems and platforms.

5\. Your Choices

a) Opting Out of Promotional Messages: You may choose not to receive our promotional communications by clicking the “My Account” tab and clicking the “My Settings” and “Preferences” tabs. You may also click the unsubscribe link in the footer of any e-mail or newsletter you receive. You may also e-mail us at privacy@bold.com.

b) Update/Delete or Change Your Resume or Cover Letter: To change or delete your resumes or cover letters, login to your Provider account and click “Resume” and “Cover Letter” tabs and select edit or delete.

c) Site Privacy Settings: Information that you disclose while participating on the Site may be public and subject to redistribution by us and any third-party that reviews your profile or information that you post. You may change preferences for other Provider services as set forth in section 8 or by contacting us as set forth in Section 15. Please be aware that Provider is not responsible for the uses, disclosures or copies of your public postings on or through the Site that you make public and that are downloaded by third parties.

d) Administrative Messages Cannot Be Turned Off: As Provider provides an on-line service you may not opt-out of administrative e-mails (for example e-mails about your transactions or policy changes) for your registered account.

e) Deactivation or Deletion of Your User Content/Account: You may request that we deactivate your account by logging into your account and clicking the “My Settings” and “Overview” tab. You may also e-mail us at privacy@bold.com. When you request that your account be deactivated your personal information, including your resume and profiles will no longer be available to you or visible to users from Provider Applications but if any of your personal information including your personal information, was previously accessed by others using Provider Applications, we are unable to delete the information from their systems. When you deactivate your personal information on Provider Applications we will retain logs and non-personally identifiable information about you along with an archival copy of your information, which is not accessible by you or third parties on Provider Applications but which might be used by us for recordkeeping and internal purposes, including enforcing this Policy and demographic, reporting and research purposes.

f) Timing and Third Parties: We will endeavor to comply with your requests as soon as reasonably possible but please note that changes requested of us may not be effective immediately. Unless required by law, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers, potential employers, job-posting sites you authorize us to contact on your behalf, or strategic or marketing partners) with whom we have already shared your information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

6\. Information You Share on the Site

If you participate in Provider services (e.g., resume posting, profile creation, Job Alerts) that permit you or Provider on your behalf to post information on third party sites (e.g., websites, bulletin boards, personal urls) and if you post information or content, such as by posting photos, or participating in online forums or communities, when you interact with our Site through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending upon your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. We cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. Please refer to those third party sites’ privacy policies and terms of use to learn more about their privacy practices, which we do not control.

a) Other services: If you use the Site, Provider may create a universal application derived from the information you provide on the Site that will be visible to potential employers who have immediate needs for prospects as well as visitors to the Site. Therefore, your Site Profile may be publically viewable. You may elect to have your Profile restricted to registered users only by following the instructions on the Site for that particular setting. You agree that employers and Provider will use the contact information you have provided to contact you by e-mail and/or SMS text and you understand that this consent is not a condition to having access to the Site or Provider services. Message and data rates may apply.

7\. Tracking Technologies (Cookies)

When you visit the Site, we and our business partners may use tracking technologies to enhance your online experience or customize our offerings. A few additional important things you should know about our use of tracking technologies (cookies):

  * We may offer certain features that are available only through the use of tracking technologies.
  * We use both session and persistent tracking technologies. Tracking technologies (e.g., cookies) can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). You are always free to decline tracking technologies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site. Refer to the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling tracking technologies such as cookies.
  * We encode and protect the tracking technologies that Provider sets, so that only we can interpret the information stored in them You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third party service providers, that we have allowed on our Site that assist us with various aspects of our Site operations and services, such as Google Analytics.
  * You also may encounter tracking technologies from third parties on certain pages of the websites that we do not control and have not authorized. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page).
  * We may target and track the videos you view on the Site. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or third party social media for up to two years or as permitted by applicable law.

For more information about the use of cookies and similar technology on our Site please review this Privacy Policy and our Tracking Technologies Policy.

8\. Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information

Registered members can review and change personal information at any time by accessing their accounts on the Site (through the My Account and My Settings tabs). You should promptly update your personal information if it changes or becomes inaccurate. We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our Terms of Use, or take other actions permitted by law. Likewise if your account or membership is terminated or suspended, we may maintain some information to prevent re-registration. For non-registered members, you may update or request to access your personal information by contacting us as set forth in Section 15.

We will endeavor to comply with your requests as soon as reasonably possible but please note that changes requested of us may not be effective immediately. Unless required by law, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party service providers, potential employers, job-posting sites you authorize us to contact on your behalf, or strategic or marketing partners) with whom we have already shared your information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

9\. Notice to California Residents

a) California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. To make such a request, please contact us at californiarequest@bold.com. For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

b) California Business & Professions Code Section 22575 (b) provides that California residents are entitled to know how Provider responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. Provider does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been adopted. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is universally accepted.

10\. Third Parties

Our Site may contain links to other third party websites and Provider may provide products and services that share information with third party sites for your job search. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party sites so it is important to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies before providing your personal information.

11\. Security

We maintain technical, physical, and administrative security measures to protect the security of your personal information against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers and information access authorization controls. It is your responsibility to make sure that your personal information is accurate.

12\. Children’s Privacy

The Site is a general audience site and it is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information via our websites, applications, services, or tools from users in this age group.  
If you are a minor and want to remove the information you posted to the Site, please contact us via the email or mailing address listed in Section 15 below. Removal of the information you posted does not ensure its complete or comprehensive removal.

13\. Storage and International Transfer

As we operate internationally, and many of our computer systems are currently based globally, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy your personal information may be stored and processed elsewhere by us, our affiliates or an unaffiliated service provider. The data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. When you create an account/profile or otherwise provide us with personal information, you consent to the collection, storage and/or processing of your personal information in the United States, Canada and other countries of your personal information and tracking technologies/cookies as described in this Privacy Policy.

14\. Notification Regarding Updates

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy posted at any time or from time to time via this Site shall be deemed to be the Privacy Policy then in effect. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Site. You should check the Site frequently for updates.

15\. Contact Us

If your questions are not answered online, you may email us at privacy@bold.com, or write to us at BOLD LLC, City View Plaza II, 48 Road 165, Suite 6000, Guaynabo, PR 00968, or using the contact us form on the Site.
